(Satori Shun) To a real lover
Isn't it good to be?
(Hattori Maika)
Don't joke.
Me and Shun
It's not worth it.
How can you look at me?
(Photon) Sunday
A dinner party with Kotone's family.
I'm not going.
(Photo) What is your will?
I haven't heard it.
Sorry for the delay.
(Kotone) Shun!
This time's story➡
What happened not
Could you please do this?
To me
There are other women who have decided on their minds.
♬〜
Slap! (The sound of a drink)
Ah.
Ah! Ah, sorry! ➡
OK?
Ah, it's okay.
Um... are you okay with that?
♬〜
Um... it's really okay...
(Kotone) No good ➡
For your clothes
Because it will cause stains.
Ah, no, but...
If so ➡
Let's exchange it for my clothes.
Huh?
Konkon (Knokku)
Rent this room. Right?
Huh?
Huh? Ah, ah... ah...
Gacha slack (door sound)
Ah, stop for a moment.
(Kotone) What?
Um...➡
Sorry, but are you an employee?
It's not.
This is my first time here.
Ah...
Did someone visit?
I've always wanted to come
To Shun's company.
"Shun-san"?
President Satori's
Do you know someone?
I know someone... That's right.
I'm not just an acquaintance though.
Hehe. ➡
yesterday
Because I couldn't talk at all ➡
If you come here, Shun-san
I thought I might meet him.
Dinner with my parents
I'm really nervous.
A dinner party with my parents...
(Recollection) Why you want to refuse marriage proposals
Can I ask? ｠
｟First of all, I am
I don't want to get married now
｟Even if you speak honestly ➡
The opponent is
Maybe it's because she's a young lady who grew up in a greenhouse?
You don't agree
Maybe you...
Did you know me?
Ah... it's Mr. Satori's fiancee
I'm listening.
Did you hear it from Shun?
happy!
About me
You're talking to me.
Hehe.
Such private matters➡
I told you about it.
With someone close to Shun
I can't help but meet you like this.
There are coincidences.
Hehe.
The opportunity to talk to people in the company
It's not that easy ➡
About Shun and Maika
I would like to ask you a lot.
Why my name...
♬〜
⚟Kong Kong
⚟Gatcha
(Akiyama) President.
(Kotone) I've never worked ➡
I admired being a company employee.
Hehe.
In the company, Shun
What kind of president is he? ➡
Even if you don't promise it to be an employee
It's great because we can meet every day.
I'm jealous.
But when I get married, mornings and nights
I can stay with you though.
Hehe.
(Voice in the heart)
<<Stay like this
I can't ignore it≫
<<In times like this, for Shun
What can you do...≫
Um...➡
Me and Shun
I'm dating you.
I'll also talk about the future as Shun-san.
From him
I've heard that the marriage proposal will be cancelled.
Hehehe. ➡
Haha. sorry.
That's a lie. ➡
About me, Shun
I know everything!
♬〜
Friendship and work-related ➡
Home environment and past
I've looked into it all.
Shun-san, you have a specific lover
It's a non-creational principle. ➡
So I'll marry myself too
I'm sure he's reluctant to do so...
you
He's just one who's convenient for you.
Poor Maika-san.
I believe in Shun.
♬〜
Shun-san!
Nothing is done?
Ah yes.
♬〜
Kotone-san, this
What exactly does it mean?
Because even if I say I want to meet
Because you won't meet.
With Shun-san and someone close to me
When we get along well➡
I wonder if they'll come.
Do this ➡
Didn't you think it would have the opposite effect?
Huh?
What involves the people around me
Please stop.
♬〜
She is for me
He's more important than anyone else.
This sort of thing already
Never do not do it.
(Piano sound)
But Shun's fiance is me!
About engagement
I should have refused the other day.
(Piano sound)
But I have to be Shun...
Even Shun-san has to be me...
You are Shun's
What do you love? ➡
face? title? ability?
Do you love all of the past?
I love everything about Shun.
(Kotone) Everything now and in the past.
♬〜
(Kotone) To Shun
There was a difficult past ➡
Did you know? ➡
I understand all of that past
I'm confident that I can heal. ➡
If it were me...
♬〜
Will it heal?
You're the wounds of others
You don't realize you're going to gooey.
♬〜
Maika Return to work.
Ah... Yes.
♬〜
Shun-san ➡
Are you Kagaya-kun?
♬〜
｟Don! ｠
(Boys)
｟Ahhh I couldn't see it｠
(Kozue) ｟I'm being bullied again. ➡
Kagaya doesn't rebel
You're being looked up to
♬〜
｟Kagaya-kun｠
⦅Are you okay? ｠
｟Ah... yes｠
<Kagaya-kun is
Even in the class, he is quiet.
Taking advantage of that, the boys
It was often teased≫
｟It's good Hattori-san｠
｟Even if you're involved with me
There's no benefit
No matter how difficult it is➡
More than myself
He was a person who thought about people≫
｟It has nothing to do with profit or loss
｟This situation
It's harder to ignore it
｟Wow
You're reading a difficult book
｟I'm just novels
｟Novel... do you like it? ｠
｟Handsome
It seems like he likes to read books
⦅thank you! ｠
<<To each other
I know I like reading ➡
Lending and borrowing books
I started talking.
<<With Kagaya-kun
I feel very calm ➡
I felt like I had a good connection.
<<When I'm with Shun-san ➡
Like back then
My heart was at ease ➡
It was because Kagaya-kun.
｟When I'm with Shun...｠
｟I feel safe｠
(Mashima) Hattori-san Please this.
yes.
♬〜
｟How can you look at me? ｠
｟Shun? ｠
Kagaya-kun...
Did I notice, Shun?
♬〜
Beep (IC card authentication sound)
Ah...
<<Farewell to Kagaya-kun?
It was sudden≫
｟This book
I read about halfway through
⦅copper? interesting? ｠
⦅Yeah. Ah, hey
Can I borrow a little more? ｠
⦅of course⦆
⦅thank you⦆
♬〜
｟Hattori is... I love it｠
｟Eh? ｠
｟⚟(students) hahaha
♬〜
｟Tomorrow at 5am➡
I'll be waiting in the usual park
<What is Kagaya's feelings?
I was happy≫
♬〜
｟Ha! ｠
(Naomi) ｟A friend I'm dating
You have to choose it. ➡
With children with low status
Even if you go on a date ➡
To you
Because it's not worth anything. ➡
That girl doesn't even look like it ➡
Even at school
Are you being bullied? ➡
It seems like he doesn't have a father either ➡
From now on
What kind of friends do you want to date?
Properly
I'll tell my mom. ➡
It's for you
<<A loved one
To say that like that ➡
I thought it was terrible≫
"I thought I couldn't forgive you"
(Naomi)｟Let's have dinner｠
I can't say a word...≫
<<In the park where I made a promise to reply
I couldn't go≫
>
In some way, Kagaya-kun
I feel like I'm hurting it≫
♬〜
<<After that ➡
immediately
Kagaya-kun has transferred schools≫
♬〜
Straight
He conveyed my feelings ➡
I can't express my true feelings
It's over≫
📱
Tap (Mobile operation sound)
hello.
📱 It's been a while.
Sorry I couldn't contact you.
No, you're busy
thank you.
Um~➡
To me, Shun
I have something I want to ask.
📱 It was just right.
I also had something I wanted to talk about. ➡
Today
Let's break down the fake love relationship.
Huh?
📱 What about Kotone-san?
Officially
The engagement was to be broken off. ➡
Thanks to Maika. thank you.
♬〜
is that so.
I'm glad that it was helpful.
With this
Let's all be done with each other's problems now➡
You also need to pretend to be a lover
It's gone ➡
Contact outside of work
I'll try to refrain from doing that in the future.
Ah, huh, Shun-san, me...
📱 Sorry. I have to go back to work.
I'll cut it.
♬〜
That's it...
Hmm...
♬〜
I'm not going to take revenge.
In the end, it just made me feel even more painful.
♬〜
⦅Maika! ⦆
⦅president⦆
It was a fake relationship though ➡
That kindness too➡
Something to mislead others
Maybe but...≫
｟I'm sorry for making you feel so bad｠
♬〜
Konkon
⚞(Akiyama) Yes.
Excuse me.
that…
Is there a president?
(Akiyama) President from today
I've been on vacation for a while.
Was that so?
(Akiyama) Is it urgent?
Ah, no, I'll change it after my holidays.
(Mitsuko) Akiyama!
Don't you know where Shun is yet?
Miss Mitsuko.
(Photo) Ha... ➡
At such a critical time
I wonder what you're taking a leisurely rest. ➡
It's an engagement
Even though it's been blank.
(Photons)
Anyway, when Shun comes home ➡
I'll come to me soon
Please tell me. ➡
I'll go ahead with another matchmaking.
What do I think about this
I think I set it up.
He's really unusable.
Shun-san is
For the company
I'm working hard.
"Shun-san"? ➡
Who is this kid? You're just an employee, right?
(Akiyama) Yes.
I'm late to say this.
My name is Hattori Maika from the Sales Planning Department.
I can't believe it's Shun
I stopped listening to what I said ➡
Is it your fault?
♬〜
Shun's feelings➡
Would you like to respect it?
It's not going to be a story. ➡
Shun's marriage
It will have a big impact on the future of this company.
Do you know the importance of this?
With you, an employee ➡
What you're holding is different.
♬〜
You too➡
Be aware of your own body.
♬〜
Because there is a plan for a matchmaking session
I'm going back. ➡
Please contact me.
Sorry I can't help but
What a favorable thing
I'll say it.
home.
The president is in a relationship with Mitsuko
I've been worried about it for a long time, so ➡
Hattori's feelings
I'm happy.
I….
For Shun
What can we do?
To Shun
I've had a lot of help but ➡
Shun's worries are
In the end, nothing was resolved...
It can't be of any use at all.
What Hattori can do?
There are still.
Huh?
(Akiyama) President recently ➡
It seemed like something was pondering.
Hattori-san, the CEO's thoughts
Maybe I can get it.
Where is Shun?
I don't know where I'm going.
But the president is now
From past ties
To be released ➡
I think they're leaving here.
past….
♬〜
The president always says ➡
I was caring about you.
♬〜
<<The same regret as that time
I don't want to do it≫
<<A true feeling
I don't want to be able to tell you.
♬〜
<<Good memories in this city
There was almost none≫
<<Forever ➡
Hearing a heavy, pressured feeling
I thought I would live.
｟Kagaya-kun｠
⦅Are you okay? ｠
≪You're
It changed my world≫
♬〜
Time with you
I wanted to cherish it≫
♬〜
In the end, I'm
I was only thinking about myself.
♬〜
>
Let's make a break this time≫
⚟Shun! Ha ha ha...
i got you.
♬〜
This is how we can be together
I'm happy.
What if Photon does nothing
I can't believe it.
I'll definitely protect her.
Maika-chan too ➡
He was shrewd.
When I'm with my mother ➡
I feel like I'm choking up.
I was saved by you again.
i love you.
Me too.
Maika is transferred to Osaka
Did you know?
This is Kato Yugo from the same team.
thank you.
My mother is
It may be something that was set up.
Something is wrong.